faceyourmanga.it 2017-02-07

# FaceYourManga

This document aims to describe how the "faceyourmanga.com" (the site), belonging to TO UP S.r.l. ("To Up") works regarding user's personal data processing, consulting " the site" and of the services that through the site are available, as through events, exhibitions, initiatives. Within this statement describes how TO Up collect, register, and use personal data referring to User. At the same time describes the choices the user can do regarding as to the manner and aims of personal data processing from TO UP The informative report, as for art. 13 D. Lgs 196/2003- Code regarding the protection of personal data- is meant for those who connect to the institutional site www.faceyourmanga.com. The informative report takes into account also the Raccomandazione n. 2/2991 that European boards have adopted for the protection of personal data and to find some minimum rules to collect personal data on line. The report regards only the site www.faceyourmanga.com. and not any other websites user may consult by means of other link. 

"Holder" of treatment

Following the consultation of this Site data of identified or identifiable people may be treated.  
The "owner" of the data treatment is TO UP S.r.l., sited in Roma (Italia) via Palasciano n. 24, 00151 

Place of Data Treatment 

The treatments connected with web service of this site take place at the official site of the company and are handled only by specialized staff in charge of the treatment, or other temporary maintenance staff. 

No data deriving from the web service is communicated or spread to third parties, unless it is strictly necessary in order to sell commercialized products to users, through our site ( ex. delivery of an order). Any way. TO UP S.r.l. doesn't guarantee nor it is responsible for the use of user's personal data from other companies. 

The personal data provided by clients who will send request of access to our services on line, to our community, or where it is possible, meant for the purchase of our products/services and are used only instrumentally for these aims. TO UP S.r.l. will use with that aim the data put by the client, treating them by computer or with means suitable to guarantee the privacy as D.P.R. n. 318/99 with controlled access and limited to authorized subjects. All data will be preserved on software at the official site of TO UP Srl as for legal regulations time. 

Types of data treated

Surfing elements Computing system and software procedures for the functioning of this website, acquire during their normal use some personal data whose transmission is implicit in the use of Internet communication protocol. 

They are information which have not been collected to be associated to identified person concerned, but for their nature itself could allow the identification of users through information data processing, done by others. In this category of data there are the address IP or the dominion computer's names used by users who connect to the site, URI (Uniform Resource Identifier)Address of the required resources, time of request, method used to make the request to the server, the size of the file had as an answer, numerical code showing the state of the answer given by the server ( well done, error) and other parameter connected to the operative system and user's computing environment. These data are used just to have anonymous statistical information on the use of the site and to check the correct functioning and they are erased just after the elaboration. The data could be used to check out the responsibility , in case of computer offence against the site. Except in that case, at moment the information on web contact last only seven days. 

Data voluntary provided by User to handle the purchase order. 

Any optional, explicit and voluntary enter of personal data , to the address indicated on this site, in order to enter to specific services, or to use e-mail, implies that TO UP acquires the sender's address or any other personal data which will be treated exclusively to reply the request or to supply services. 

The enter of data to fulfil an order from the client, implies the acquisition of sender's address, name, surname, e-mail address or other personal data entered on line, and they will be used just to complete the order and send it. In case data are not supplied it might be impossible to fulfil the order.. 

COOKIES

No User's personal data are acquired by the site.  
No use of Cookies is done to transmit personal information, nor any kind of c.d. cookies are used, as for example a way to trace users. The use of session c.d. cookies (those ones which are not memorized in a lasting way on user's computer and disappear when the browser is closed) is strictly limited to the transmission of session identifications ( made by random number generated by the server) essential to permit a safe and efficient use of the Site. 

Session c.d. cookies used in this site avoid to use other computer technique which may be damaging to user's surfing privacy and they don't allow the acquisition of user's personal data identification. 

Treatment procedure

The data here supplied, as art. 13…….".safeguarding of one's rights relating the respect of personal data", are used in the activity of our firm for:  
1) aims connected with the management of relationship with the compiler (internal statistics, satisfaction feed back, previous acquisition of information for the conclusion of a contract or to the supply of a service, etc.);  
2) aims connected to what Law admit  
3) aims meant to the management of the Company ( as sale of goods and services on line). 

Users may exercise a right according art. 7 Act 196/2003.  
In this case the person concerned may contact the Company at its e-mail address, and provide his data. The person responsible for the treatment of data made by TO UP, with official site in Via Palasciano, 24 Rome, is the Manager of the Company, working at the same address, and who can be contacted at [info@faceyourmanga.com](mailto:info@faceyourmanga.com)

Concerned people's rights (enter right to personal data)

People who personal data are referred to have the right at any moment to obtain the confirmation of the existence or not of those data and to know the content and the origin, to check the correctness, or ask the completion or updating, or a correction (art.7 del d.lgs n.196/2003). As for the same Act you may ask the cancellation or transformation in an anonym form or to block the Data used against law, or, in any case , to oppose for right reasons, to their treatment. The request are to be sent to [privacy@faceyourmanga.com](mailto:privacy@faceyourmanga.com)

CHILDREN AND PRIVACY

TO UP is conscious that the Site and the services may be of children's interest. Nevertheless , we don't collect on purpose children under 12 's personal data. TO UP suggests parents to spend their time with their children when they are on line, and we also suggest them to teach their children how to behave when in contact with unknown people, and never to share personal data on line ( as real name, address or telephone numbers). In some jurisdictions, a notification or written permission or consent from parents is required, or even from a legal guardian for children under 12.

ALTERATION TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Stating that TO UP will never do operation of treatment different from those clearly authorized and/or required from any User, this informative report may be changed to be adapted to new legal rules, or to different policy for the treatment of data of TO UP.  
Any update informative report is available on the Site in the proper section: TO UP invites all Users to consult periodically the Site to be always informed about the last version loaded. 

For any other information on this informative report please contact us sending an e-mail to [privacy@faceyoumanga.com](mailto:privacy@faceyoumanga.com).
